Let me demonstrate the CipherOwl Watcher, and Explorer.
CipherOwl Watcher is a Chrome extension working together with our SaaS product.
Here we have a high-risk address to examine.
This address has been exposed to an entity called Excoino, which is marked as sanctioned.
Let's examine the metadata here.
Our proprietary model
filters out less likely labels,
such as ransom label in this case.
You can review the history
to see the origin of these labels, when they were collected, where they are from,and how they evolved.
Moving to transactions, you'll see
a complete list of activities.
Each entry represents a transaction
for this particular address.
You can navigate through transactions
by clicking and exploring each one.
Not only that, you can track
each specific UTXO's origin.
and destination in the system.
We call this "infinite flow". It is super powerful for fund tracing.
You can trace each address in the flows like this,
and check address risks with CipherOwl Watcher, let's try it out!
CipherOwl Watcher has identified
84 BTC addresses on this page.
CipherOwl Watcher is capable of scanning the thousands of addresses in a few seconds, in batch risk assessment mode.
With one click, we can scan
and analyze all these addresses.
We can sort and examine
each case individually.
Here are the detailed exposure metrics, which we can visualize in graphs too.
Let's click the reporting generation to ask AI to generate a report, it will take 15 seconds, will come back to this later.
In the transaction panel, addresses were highlighed by the CipherOwl Watcher:
Red for high risk,
Green for low risk,
Yellow for medium risk.
Let's examine why this particular
address shows medium risk.
We can analyze its exposure... as you can see, it is marked as noKYC, that means it is related to a KYC-free service.
Last, here is the report generated by our AI agent. Will come back to this in a separate video. That concludes our demonstration. Thank you!